A Guide to the International Society for Third-Sector Research (ISTR) records FA1838
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Conference Planning Material, 1990-2018; 4; 15.95 Cubic Feet 42 letter document boxes
  - 4th International Conference - Dublin, Ireland, 1997-2000
    - Dublin - General, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 473)
    - Dublin - General, 1999 (Box 110, Folder 1263)
    - Rooming Scholarship Recipients, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 234)
    - Poster Sessions, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 235)
    - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 236)
    - Logistics Correspondence, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 237)
    - Conference Schedule, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 238)
    - Conference Brochure, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 239)
    - Keynote Speaker, David Korten, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 240)
    - Civil Society Plenary, 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 241)
    - Commonwealth Study, 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 242)
    - "Civilizing Society" Keynote Speech, David Korten, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 243)
    - Globalization Plenary, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 244)
    - Plenaries, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 245)
    - Memos, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 246)
    - Session Moderators, 1998-2000 (Box 23, Folder 247)
    - Conference Publication, 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 248)
    - Registration Subsidies, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 384)
    - Postgrad Scholarships, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 385)
    - Developing Countries Scholarships, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 386)
    - Arab Network, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 387)
    - Central and Eastern Europe, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 388)
    - Asia, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 389)
    - Africa, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 390)
    - Latin America, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 391)
    - TARA Proposal, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 392)
    - Conference Partners, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 393)
    - Conference Issues, 1998-2000 (Box 40, Folder 394)
    - Academic Committee, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 395)
    - Conference Abstract Volume, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 475)
    - Call for Contributions, 1999-2000 (Box 47, Folder 476)
    - Working Papers Series, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 478)
    - Completed Evaluation Forms, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 479)
    - \Working Papers Consent Forms, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 480)
    - Conference Committee, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 900)
  - 5th International Conference - Cape Town, South Africa, 1998-2005
    - Working Papers, 1998-2003 (Box 22, Folder 227)
    - Schedule and General Information, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 477)
    - Scholarships, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 481)
    - Thank Yous, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 482)
    - Plenary, Civil Societies as Agents of Global (Dis)Order, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 483)
    - Keynote, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 484)
    - Sen, Amartya, 1999-2001 (Box 48, Folder 485)
    - Conference Evaluations, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 486)
    - Conference Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 487)
    - Publications Room, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 488)
    - Celebrating the Society's 10th Anniversary, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 489)
    - Site Issues, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 490)
    - Sponsorships, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 491)
    - Security, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 492)
    - Reception, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 493)
    - Meals, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 494)
    - University of Cape Town (UCT) Fuller Hall, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 495)
    - Working Papers, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 496)
    - Completed Guiding Sheets, Working Papers Volume, 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 497)
    - Conference Issues, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 498)
    - Conference Contract, Global Conferences, Ltd., 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 499)
    - Call for Contributions, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 543)
    - University of Cape Town Financials, 2002-2003 (Box 54, Folder 545)
    - Conference Proposal, 2002-2005 (Box 54, Folder 546)
    - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation Proposal, 2001-2005 (Box 54, Folder 547)
    - Open Society Foundation for South Africa Proposal, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 548)
    - Funder's Dinner, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 549)
    - W.K. Kellogg Foundation Proposal, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 550)
    - Ford Foundation Proposal, 2001-2002 (Box 54, Folder 551)
    - Fundraising, 2000-2002 (Box 54, Folder 552)
  - 6th International Conference - Toronto, Canada, 2000-2005
    - Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council of Canada (SSHRC), 2003-2004 (Box 44, Folder 440)
    - Poster Award, 2004-2005 (Box 44, Folder 441)
    - Toronto Program, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 442)
    - Meeting of Centre Directors, Toronto, Canada, 2004 July 10 (Box 45, Folder 444)
    - Conference Committee, 2002-2004 (Box 45, Folder 453)
    - Conference Bags, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 454)
    - Toronto - General, 2002-2004 (Box 45, Folder 455)
    - Conference Brochure, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 456)
    - Printer and Photographer, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 457)
    - Translation, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 458)
    - Entertainment, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 459)
    - Abstract and Theme Choices, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 460)
    - Conference Evaluations, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 461)
    - Registrations, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 462)
    - Scholarships, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 463)
    - Keynote, Eddin Ibrahim, 2000-2004 (Box 46, Folder 464)
    - Keynote Options, 2003-2004 (Box 46, Folder 465)
    - Plenary, Batliwala/Singer, Paul, 2003-2004 (Box 46, Folder 466)
    - Working Papers and Moderator Forms, 2002-2004 (Box 46, Folder 467)
    - Call for Contributions, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 468)
    - Budget, 2003-2004 (Box 110, Folder 1260)
    - Ryerson University Contract, 2003-2004 (Box 110, Folder 1261)
    - Publishers, 2004 (Box 110, Folder 1262)
  - 7th International Conference - Bangkok, Thailand, 2004-2006
    - Royal Orchard Sheraton Hotel, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 396)
    - Conference Site, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 397)
    - Abstract Acceptance/Rejection Letter Templates, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 398)
    - Moderators, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 399)
    - Call for Contributors, 2004-2005 (Box 40, Folder 400)
    - Bangkok - General, 2004-2006 (Box 40, Folder 401)
    - Evaluations, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 402)
    - Fundacao Calouste Gulbenkian, 2005-2006 (Box 41, Folder 403)
    - Conference Report, circa 2006 (Box 41, Folder 404)
    - Conference Committee, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 405)
    - Conference Issues, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 406)
    - Registration Subsidies, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 407)
    - Scholarships, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 408)
    - African Scholarships, 2005-2006 (Box 41, Folder 409)
    - Abstracts, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 410)
    - Publisher Room, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 411)
    - Translator, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 412)
    - Sasakawa Peace Foundation, 2005-2006 (Box 41, Folder 413)
    - Funder Prospects, 2005-2006 (Box 41, Folder 414)
    - Contacts, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 415)
    - Foundation Backgrounds, 2004-2006 (Box 41, Folder 416)
    - Masa Deguchi Fundraising, 2005-2006 (Box 41, Folder 417)
    - Support, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 418)
    - Participant List, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 419)
    - Name Tags, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 420)
    - Keynote Address, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 421)
    - Program Changes, circa 2006 (Box 41, Folder 422)
    - Conference Packet, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 423)
    - Conference Program, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 469)
    - Program Printing, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 470)
  - 8th International Conference - Barcelona, Spain, 2005-2010
    - Gulbenkian Foundation Scholarship, 2008-2009 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Gulbenkian Foundation, 2008-2010 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Reception, Princess Sofia, 2007-2008 (Box 87, Folder 934)
    - University Catering, 2007-2008 (Box 87, Folder 935)
    - Posters, 2008 (Box 87, Folder 936)
    - Reception Venues, 2006-2008 (Box 87, Folder 937)
    - Rocio Nogales Correspondence, 2007 (Box 87, Folder 938)
    - EMES, 2007-2008 (Box 87, Folder 939)
    - EMES/ISTR Memorandum of Understanding, 2007-2009 (Box 87, Folder 940)
    - Workshop/Bertelsmann, 2007-2008 (Box 87, Folder 941)
    - Panel Proposals, 2007 (Box 87, Folder 942)
    - Conference Program Ideas, 2006-2007 (Box 87, Folder 943)
    - Heidelberg Meeting Agenda, 2007-2008 (Box 87, Folder 944)
    - Conference Committee, Heidelberg, 2007 (Box 87, Folder 945)
    - Conference Statistics, 2006-2008 (Box 87, Folder 946)
    - University of Barcelona, Business School, 2007 (Box 87, Folder 947)
    - Spanish Foundation Centre, 2007 (Box 87, Folder 948)
    - Fundación Luis Vives, 2007-2008 (Box 87, Folder 949)
    - CINEFOGO (Civil Society and New Forms of Governance), 2006-2008 (Box 87, Folder 950)
    - Conference Evaluation, 2008 (Box 88, Folder 951)
    - Caja Madrid, 2008 (Box 88, Folder 952)
    - Spanish Foundations - BBVA, La Caixa, 2007 (Box 88, Folder 953)
    - Mapfre Foundation, 2008 (Box 88, Folder 954)
    - King Baudoin Foundation, 2005-2007 (Box 88, Folder 955)
    - Caxia Catalunya, 2007 (Box 88, Folder 956)
    - Volkswagen Foundation, 2007 (Box 88, Folder 957)
    - Telefonica Foundation, Spain, 2007 (Box 88, Folder 958)
    - Fundación Bertelsmann, 2007-2008 (Box 88, Folder 959)
    - Youth Engagement Roundtable, 2008 (Box 88, Folder 960)
    - Sessions, 2007-2008 (Box 88, Folder 961)
    - Atlas Review, 2007-2008 (Box 88, Folder 962)
    - Grading Sheets - Theme Chairs, 2007-2008 (Box 89, Folder 963)
    - Conference Academic Committee, 2007 (Box 89, Folder 964)
    - Conference Contributions, 2007 (Box 89, Folder 965)
    - Working Papers, 2006-2009 (Box 89, Folder 966)
    - Working Papers Evaluation Forms, 2008 (Box 89, Folder 967)
    - Working Papers Consent Forms, 2009 (Box 89, Folder 968)
    - Margery Daniels Visit, 2007-2008 (Box 90, Folder 979)
    - Heidelberg Meeting, 2007-2008 (Box 90, Folder 980)
    - 2010 Conference Sites, 2007-2008 (Box 90, Folder 981)
    - Tone Tveit Issues (World Travel Links), 2007 (Box 90, Folder 982)
    - Conference Participant Lists, 2006-2010 (Box 90, Folder 983)
    - International Marketing Challenges, 2007 (Box 90, Folder 984)
    - Iberia Airlines, 2007 (Box 90, Folder 985)
    - Exhibition for the Incentive Business Travel and Meetings (EIBTM) Meeting, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 986)
    - Conference Brochure, 2007 (Box 90, Folder 987-988)
    - Invitation Letters, 2008 (Box 90, Folder 989)
    - Participant List, 2008 (Box 91, Folder 990)
    - Refund Requests, 2008 (Box 91, Folder 991)
    - Conference Bags, 2008 (Box 91, Folder 992)
    - Conference Bags, Logos, Shawls, CDs, 2008 (Box 91, Folder 993)
    - General, 2007 (Box 91, Folder 994)
    - Penyafort, 2007-2008 (Box 91, Folder 995)
    - Student Travel Program, 2007 (Box 91, Folder 996)
    - Perez Diaz, Keynote Speaker, 2007-2008 (Box 91, Folder 997)
    - Plenary - Theorizing the Global Third Sector: Does North/South Makes Sense, 2007-2008 (Box 91, Folder 998)
    - Workshops, 2007-2008 (Box 91, Folder 999)
    - Moderators, 2008 (Box 91, Folder 1000)
    - Special Requests, 2008 (Box 91, Folder 1001)
    - Senator Hotel, 2007-2008 (Box 91, Folder 1005)
    - Princess Sofia Hotel, 2007-2008 (Box 91, Folder 1006)
    - Resa, 2007-2008 (Box 91, Folder 1007)
    - Constanza, 2007 (Box 91, Folder 1008)
    - Hotels, 2007-2008 (Box 92, Folder 1009)
    - St. Jordi Meeting, 2007-2008 (Box 92, Folder 1010)
    - Caterer, 2008 (Box 92, Folder 1011)
    - Building/Organizational Details, 2008 (Box 92, Folder 1012)
    - Audiovisual Details, 2008 (Box 92, Folder 1013)
    - United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), 2008 (Box 92, Folder 1014)
    - Scholarship Lists, 2008 (Box 92, Folder 1015)
    - Scholarship Support, 2008 (Box 92, Folder 1016)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center Workshop, 2008 (Box 92, Folder 1017)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center, 2007-2008 (Box 92, Folder 1018)
    - Centres Directors Meeting, 2008 (Box 92, Folder 1019)
    - Conference Statistics, undated (Box 110, Folder 1264)
  - 9th International Conference - Istanbul, Turkey, 2000-2010
    - Special Session, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Workshops, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Third Sector Foundation of Turkey (TUSEV) Current, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Kadir Has University, 2007-2010 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Oxford Abstracts, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Poster Presentations, undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Conference Evaluations, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Conference Planning, 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Koch, Dirk-Jan, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Koch, Dirk-Jan - ISTR ESDA, undated (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Istanbul, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Hotels, 2008-2009 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Sisay Gebre-Egziabher Subsidy/Scholarship, 2008-2010 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Registration Subsidies, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Fundraising, 2005-2007 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Ford Mexico, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Abstract Review, 2006-2008 (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Session Moderators, 2008-2010 (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - Turkish Airlines, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - Conference Evaluations, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - Panel Submissions, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 90-91)
    - Indian and Nepalese Participants, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Turkish Philanthropy Fund, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Turkish Plenary (Ahmet O. Evin), 2010 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - Potential Conference Keynote Speakers, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Keynote (Thoraya Ahmed Obaid), 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Theory Plenary, 2000-2010 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Call for Contributions, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - Affinity Group on Gender (AGG) Proposal, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - International Development Research Centre (IDRC), 2009 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - International Development Research Centre (IDRC) - Disk 1: IDRC 2009/CRDI 2009 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - International Development Research Centre (IDRC) - Disk 2: Bookcase (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - Conference Academic Committee, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - Conference Brochure, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - Conference Brochure, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 1002)
    - Conference Program, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - US Consular General, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - MBD Travel, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - Third Sector Foundation of Turkey (TUSEV) Brochure, undated (Box 12, Folder 106)
    - Advertisements, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 1003)
    - Publishers, 2010 (Box 91, Folder 1004)
  - 10th International Conference - Siena, Italy, 2004-2013
    - Working Papers, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Reviewers, 2011-2012 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Subsidy, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Tenth International Conference Evaluations, 2010-2013 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Siena, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Advertisements/Exhibits, 2010-2012 (Box 95, Folder 1050)
    - Hotels, 2012 (Box 95, Folder 1051)
    - General, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 1052)
    - Lufthansa, 2011 (Box 95, Folder 1053)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration, undated (Box 95, Folder 1054)
    - Vacanze Senesi, 2011-2012 (Box 95, Folder 1055)
    - Abstract Reviews, 2011 (Box 95, Folder 1056)
    - Conference Brochure, 2011 (Box 95, Folder 1057)
    - Website, 2011 (Box 95, Folder 1058)
    - Call for Contributions, 2011 (Box 95, Folder 1059)
    - Review Process, undated (Box 95, Folder 1060)
    - Foundation ForTes (Fondazione Scuola di Alta Formazione per il Terzo Settore), 2010-2011 (Box 95, Folder 1061)
    - Bologna, 2010 (Box 95, Folder 1062)
    - Keynote Speaker, 2011-2012 (Box 95, Folder 1063)
    - Workshops, 2011-2012 (Box 95, Folder 1064)
    - Conference Program, 2012 (Box 95, Folder 1065)
    - Special Sessions, 2011 (Box 95, Folder 1066)
    - General, 2010-2012 (Box 95, Folder 1067)
    - Moderators, 2012 (Box 96, Folder 1068)
    - Special Requests, 2012 (Box 96, Folder 1069)
    - Supplement Session, 2012 (Box 96, Folder 1070)
    - Logistics, 2012 (Box 96, Folder 1071)
    - Adriano Scarpelli, 2011-2012 (Box 96, Folder 1072)
    - Emerging Scholar Award, 2011-2012 (Box 96, Folder 1073)
    - Working Papers, 2004-2012 (Box 96, Folder 1074)
    - Video, 2012-2013 (Box 96, Folder 1075)
    - Poster Award, 2012 (Box 96, Folder 1076)
    - Evaluation, 2012 (Box 96, Folder 1077)
    - Participants, 2012 (Box 96, Folder 1078)
    - Academic Conference Committee, 2011-2012 (Box 96, Folder 1078)
    - Conference Site, 2010-2012 (Box 96, Folder 1079)
    - PhD Seminar, 2011-2012 (Box 102, Folder 1160)
    - Birmingham Conference, 2010 (Box 110, Folder 1265)
    - Hong Kong, 2010 (Box 110, Folder 1266)
  - 11th International Conference - Münster, Germany, 2011-2014
    - Member Letters, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Muenster, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Ads/Exhibits, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Moderator Forms, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Conference Evaluations, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Working Paper Evaluations, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Working Papers, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - PhD Seminar, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Reviewers, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - All Academic Reports, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Subsidy, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Certificates of Participation, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Community Foundation Special Session, 2014 (Box 90, Folder 975)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center Special Session, 2014 (Box 90, Folder 976)
    - China Special Session, 2014 (Box 90, Folder 977)
    - Conference Logistics, 2014 (Box 90, Folder 978)
    - Conference Site Bids, 2011-2013 (Box 96, Folder 1080)
    - Conference Schedule, 2014 (Box 96, Folder 1083)
    - Attendence, 2014 (Box 97, Folder 1084)
    - Moderators, Reviewers, Committee Members, 2014 (Box 97, Folder 1085)
    - Scheduling Requests, 2014 (Box 97, Folder 1086)
    - Subsidy Recipients, 2014 (Box 97, Folder 1087)
    - NACC/Academic Centers Meeting, 2014 (Box 97, Folder 1088)
    - Conference App, 2014 (Box 97, Folder 1089)
    - Academic Committee, 2013-2014 (Box 97, Folder 1090)
    - Hotels, 2011-2013 (Box 97, Folder 1091)
    - Call for Papers, 2011-2013 (Box 97, Folder 1092)
    - Plenary Sessions, 2012-2014 (Box 97, Folder 1093)
    - Special Sessions, 2013-2014 (Box 97, Folder 1094)
    - Special Session - Global Data on Philanthropy, 2014 (Box 97, Folder 1095)
    - General, 2011-2013 (Box 97, Folder 1096)
    - Youth Hostel, 2012-2013 (Box 102, Folder 1161)
    - PhD Seminar - Funding Proposal, 2013-2014 (Box 102, Folder 1162)
    - PhD Seminar - Applications, 2014 (Box 102, Folder 1163)
    - PhD Seminar - Faculty, 2012-2014 (Box 102, Folder 1164)
    - PhD Seminar - Students, 2013-2014 (Box 102, Folder 1165)
    - PhD Seminar, 2013-2014 (Box 102, Folder 1166)
    - Working Papers, 2014 (Box 110, Folder 1267)
  - 12th International Conference - Stockholm, Sweden, 2012-2016
    - Reviewers, 2015-2016 (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - Atanto App, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 108)
    - Subsidy, 2016 (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Miscellaneous, 2016 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - Participants, 2016 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Working Papers, 2016 (Box 13, Folder 112)
    - Moderator Evaluation, 2016 (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Conference Logistics, 2016 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - Conference Plenary, 2015-2016 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Brasilia, 2012-2013 (Box 96, Folder 1081)
    - Conference App, 2014-2016 (Box 100, Folder 1118)
    - Lecture - Stanley Katz, 2015-2016 (Box 100, Folder 1119)
    - Conference Program, 2015 (Box 100, Folder 1120)
    - Academic Committee, 2015-2016 (Box 100, Folder 1121)
    - Call for Contributions, 2016 (Box 100, Folder 1122)
    - Preliminary Visit, 2015 (Box 100, Folder 1123)
    - Keynote, 2014-2016 (Box 100, Folder 1124)
    - PhD Seminar - Applications, 2015 (Box 102, Folder 1167)
    - PhD Seminar - Travel Requests, 2016 (Box 102, Folder 1168)
    - PhD Seminar - Faculty, 2015-2016 (Box 102, Folder 1169)
    - PhD Seminar - Students, 2015-2016 (Box 102, Folder 1170)
    - PhD Seminar, 2015-2016 (Box 102, Folder 1171)
    - PhD Seminar - China Proposal, 2015-2016 (Box 102, Folder 1172)
    - General, 2013-2014 (Box 110, Folder 1268)
    - Logistics, 2015 (Box 110, Folder 1269)
    - Special Sessions, 2015 (Box 110, Folder 1270)
    - Philanthropy Panel, 2015 (Box 110, Folder 1271)
  - 13th International Conference - Amsterdam, The Netherlands, 2013-2018
    - Sign-in Sheets, 2018 (Box 14, Folder 124)
    - Working Papers, 2018 (Box 14, Folder 125)
    - General, 2015-2016 (Box 14, Folder 126, 128-129)
    - Special Requests, 2018 (Box 14, Folder 127)
    - Registrations, 2018 (Box 20, Folder 206)
    - Evaluations, 2018 (Box 20, Folder 207)
    - Canada Submissions, 2017-2018 (Box 20, Folder 208)
    - Megan Conference, 2017-2018 (Box 20, Folder 209)
    - Schedule, 2018 (Box 20, Folder 210)
    - Academic Committee Meeting, 2016-2018 (Box 21, Folder 211)
    - Conference Issues, 2017-2018 (Box 21, Folder 212)
    - Call for Papers, 2017-2018 (Box 21, Folder 213)
    - Memorandum of Understanding (MOU), 2018 (Box 21, Folder 214)
    - Logistics, 2017-2018 (Box 21, Folder 215)
    - International Comparative Policy Analysis Forum/Journal of Comparative Policy Analysis Workshop, 2017-2018 (Box 21, Folder 216)
    - Keynote, 2017-2018 (Box 21, Folder 217)
    - General, 2017-2018 (Box 21, Folder 218)
    - PhD Seminar, 2016 (Box 21, Folder 219)
    - Academic Program, 2017-2018 (Box 21, Folder 220)
    - Oxflamation Session, 2018 (Box 21, Folder 221)
    - Conference Site, 2013 (Box 96, Folder 1082)
    - PhD Seminar, 2017-2018 (Box 110, Folder 1272)
- Conference Programs, 1994-2012; 5; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
  Series 5 contains printed versions of ISTR's international conference programs.
  - Inaugural Conference: Towards the Year 2000, Hungary, 1994 July 4-7 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Second International Conference, Mexico, 1996 July 18-21 (Box 4, Folder 36-37)
  - Third International Conference, Switzerland, 1998 July 8-11 (Box 5, Folder 38-39)
  - Working Papers from the Third International Conference, Switzerland, 1998 July 8-11 (Box 5, Folder 40-41)
  - Fourth International Conference, Ireland, 2000 July 5-8 (Box 6, Folder 42-43)
  - Fifth Biennial Conference, South Africa, 2002 July 7-10 (Box 6, Folder 44-45)
  - Sixth International Conference, Canada, 2004 July 11-14 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Sixth International Conference, Canada, 2004 July 11-14 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Seventh International Conference, Thailand, 2006 July 9-12 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Seventh International Conference, Thailand, 2006 July 9-12 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Eighth International Conference and Second European Conference of the EME European Research Network and ISTR, Spain, 2008 July 9-12 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Eighth International Conference and Second European Conference of the EME European Research Network and ISTR, Spain, 2008 July 9-12 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Ninth International Conference, Turkey, 2010 July 7-10 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Tenth International Conference, Italy, 2012 July 10-13 (Box 7, Folder 50-51)
- Voluntas: International Journal of Voluntary and Nonprofit Organizations, 1990-2021; 6; 8.73 Cubic Feet 23 letter document boxes
  Series 6 contains information about ISTR's Voluntas journal. Voluntas includes articles and book reviews about the nonprofit sector and civil society. Copies of Voluntas (volumes 1-32) can be found in Series 6.1.
  - Editor Search, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Voluntas Book Proposal, 2008-2010 (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - Africa Special Issue, 2010-2011 (Box 14, Folder 132)
  - Latin American Special Issue, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - Volunteering and Volunteerism Special Issue (Fall 2010), 2008 (Box 15, Folder 134)
  - Rupert Taylor Contract, 2000-2003 (Box 15, Folder 135)
  - Rupert Taylor Correspondence, 2001-2008 (Box 15, Folder 136)
  - Springer (Rupert Taylor), 2005 (Box 15, Folder 137)
  - Sage Publishers - Publisher Search, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 138)
  - General, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 139)
  - Withdrawn Article - "Who Gives? Experimental Evidence" Avner Ben-Ner, et al, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 140)
  - Plenum Press, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 141)
  - Manchester University Press, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 142)
  - Kluwer Web, Plenum Press Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 15, Folder 143)
  - Evaluation, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 144)